在低迷的房地产市场中 明智投资的五大秘诀就是
So the five keys to investing wisely in a down real estate market are...
"诀"对保持冷静
KEYp your cool...
"诀"对信息灵通
KEYp informed...
腿脚勤快
Legwork.
我刚成为一家新房地产公司的合伙人
I recently became a partner in a new agency,
所以我要办个解说会
so I put together a seminar
来吸引第一次买房的新手
to recruit first-time home buyers.
我希望给他们一步步讲解
I want to give 'em a step-by-step description
我如何帮他们选到满意的房子
of exactly what I can do for them.
你问我会不会担心他们记下步骤后
Am I worried tha they might write it all down
自己去挑选房子
and just do it themselves?
坦白说 我现在才察觉到这个问题
Quite frankly, I hadn't thought about it until just now.
我非得去参加吗
Do I really have to go to this thing?
当然 你今天戏份大着呢
Yes. You're a big part of today.
你是我的后勤人员
You're my support staff.
那你为什么不付我工钱
Then why am I not getting paid?
问得好
That is a good question.
我会把答案用短信发到
And I think I'm gonna text you the answer
我们买给你的手机上
on that cell phone we pay for.
亲爱的 要再练习一下你的部分吗
Honey, do you wanna practice your part again?
不 就一个问题而已 我记住了
Uh, no. It's just one question. I think I got it.
是的 可那是最关键的问题
Yeah, but it's the most important question
它将引出我的压轴好戏
because it launches me into my big finish.
-没错 -那样人们会高高兴兴地离开
- Yes. - That way, people leave excited.
我看是很高兴能离开吧
Oh, I think people will be excited to leave.
卢克
Luke...
你在干嘛
Why?
抱歉 我是为了完成学校作业
I'm sorry. It's for school.
我必须设计一个容器保护鸡蛋
I have to design a container that'll protect an egg
从1层楼高处跌落而不摔碎
in a 1-story drop.
好吧 所以
Yeah, so, um,
你准备用包装鸡蛋的纸盒吗
you thought you would go with an egg carton?
也许最佳方法就藏在我眼皮底下呢
What if the best idea was under my nose the whole time?
你得下来把这一摊收拾干净
You're gonna need to come down and clean this up now.
其实我本来完全不用瞎折腾的
Ugh! I wouldn't have to do any of this
都怪艾丽克斯不肯让我用她当年上这课时的作品
if Alex would just let me use hers from when she took the class.
门都没有
Never.
那设计是我的知识产权
That design is my intellectual property.
我觉得它足以应用在无人"驾"驶太空飞行上
I think it has applications for unmanned space flight.
你再继续当科学怪胎
Keep talking like that
一辈子都无人可"嫁"了
and you'll go through life unmanned.
-真会搞笑 -姑娘们
- Funny. - Girls.
卢克 亲爱的 听我说
Luke, honey, listen to me.
你得独立完成这个作业
You're gonna need to do this project on your own.
你能做到的 只要努力动动脑子
And you can do it. Just... really think.
我想到了
I've got it!
用我自身做容器如何
What if I'm the container?
算是个想法 你可以...
There's a thought. You could be...
别 卢克 卢克
No, Luke! Luke!
好 好 亲亲 爱你哦
Okay, si, te quiero. Mwah, mwah, mwah!
我听懂了"疯老巫婆子"
I understood "Crazy old witch,"
"去死吧" 以及 "爱你哦"
"Go kill yourself," Then "I love you."
我一直搞不懂 你们家人怎么老互相嚷嚷
I'll never get this, how you all yell at each other.
如何感受家人爱
That's how you know that your family loves you
就在他们嚷你时
when they feel free to scream at you.
那我应该对我前妻说声抱歉了
Oh, I guess I owe my ex-wife an apology.
显然 她当年爱我爱得如痴如狂
Apparently,she was nuts about me.
该死
Darn it!
下次在炒锅上试验吧
Try the next one over a frying pan.
正好给我当早饭
I could use some breakfast.
真让人丧气
This is so frustrating.
至少你是在亲自动手做事
At least you're getting your hands dirty for a change.
平时都沉迷于精神世界 现在能动动手也不错
It is a nice break from the life of the mind I usually live.
说得很对
That's the spirit.
再说也是对人类境况的一种暗喻
Plus it's a metaphor for the human condition.
我们不都是易碎的鸡蛋吗
Aren't we all just fragile eggs
躲藏在气泡垫的背后 虚张声势
hiding behind bubble wrap and bravado?
又回到老样子了
And we're back.
我保证你的鸡蛋坠落作品
Well, I'm sure that your egg-droppy thing
会是全班最棒的
is going to be the best in the class.
肯定比不上卢克的
Except for Luke's.
是吗 我们家卢克吗
Really? Our Luke?
可他不是 有点...天然呆
But isn't he, like, a little, like...
克莱尔肯定会帮他忙的
I bet Claire's gonna help him,
就像上次美术课帮他画自画像一样
just like she did with his self-portrait for art class.
那双眼睛囧囧有神
There was life in those eyes.
让人难以忘怀
It was haunting.
那行 我要将此不正之风扼杀于萌芽中
Tell you what. I'm gonna nip this in the bud.
你应该有公平竞争的机会
You deserve a fighting chance.
我是为孩子们的那个鸡蛋坠落作业打来的
Hey, I'm calling about that, uh, egg project the boys are doing.
家长不该插手帮忙 对吧
Parents aren't supposed to help out on that, right?
家长干嘛要帮呢
Why would the parents be helping?
那干嘛要帮8岁的孩子切葡萄呢
Why do they cut grapes for 8-year-olds?
我觉得他们都会啃炸鸡条了
I figure if you can eat a chicken finger,
肯定也能成功解决一颗葡萄
you can tear your way through a grape.
又旧事重提吗 爸爸
Again, dad?
抱歉 那事...
Oh, I'm sorry, it just...
总让我不爽而已
bugs me, is all.
我要说的是 我不会帮忙
The point is, I'm not helping,
我希望大家也都别帮忙
and I hope no one else is helping, either.
好吧 爸爸 多谢你提醒
Okay, dad. Thanks for the heads-up.
爱你哦 再见
Love you. Bye-bye.
我爸要帮曼尼做作业了
Well, my dad is doing Manny's project for him.
他专门打电话来告诉你吗
He called to tell you that?
不 他打来告诉我他不会帮忙
Oh, no. He called to tell me that he wasn't,
那正是当你要插手帮忙时
which is exactly what you say when you are,
又不想引人怀疑的说辞
but you don't want anybody to suspect it.
是吗
Really?
那你和你爸之间的问题又是什么说辞呢
What would you say if you had issues with your father?
克莱尔和杰非常喜欢一较高低
Claire and Jay are incredibly competitive.
网球比赛 扑克比赛 任何事
Tennis games, card games, everything.
没人知道原因
Who knows why?
克莱尔就像是我爸期望中的儿子
Claire is the son that my dad never had.
他希望有个儿子一起在后院投球玩
I mean, he just wanted someone to throw a ball in the backyard.
我投过一次 可是
I did once, but...
他没有来
He did not attend.
看起来挺有趣的
Looks like fun.
开始是 可现在变难了
It was, but now it's hard.
你一定能做得很好 老弟
Oh, I'm sure you're gonna do great, buddy...
克莱尔
Claire?
我只是对咱儿子的作品感兴趣
Uh, I am just showing interest in our son's project,
任何家长都...
which any parent would--
想想 好好想 我在想
Think! Think... to do. Thinking... I am,
或许我应该留在这儿
that maybe I should stay here
以防卢克有什么问题要问
in case Luke has any questions.
你能找到其他什么人
Do you think you can find somebody else
去帮你完成解说会吗
to help you with your seminar?
估计不行吧 现在让我去哪儿找啊
I don't know. That's a little last-minute.
你是不可替代的啊
You're kind of irreplaceable.
我意思是说 反正就只有一个问题
Well, I mean, it's just one question,
而且那个解说会也不会花太多时间
and the seminar isn't for a few hours...
喂 歌洛莉亚 帮个小忙
Hey, Gloria? Quick favor.
好吧 那边见 拜拜
Okay. See you there. Bye-bye.
什么事
What was that?
是菲尔
Phil.
他请我去帮他完成一个解说会
He needs help with a seminar that he's giving.
怎么不找克莱尔帮他
Why can't Claire help him?
-他没说 -我告诉你为什么
- He didn't say. - I'll tell you why
因为她投身于卢克的鸡蛋坠落实验了
because she's knee-deep in Luke's egg drop project.
她说过不会插手帮忙的
She said that she was not going to help.
那正是我对自己的惯用说辞
That's exactly what I would say to me
用于我想帮孩子 又想骗自己说没插手的场合
if I was helping my kid and didn't want me to know.
你为什么会跟自己说话
Why would you be talking to you?
我只是说 那样对曼尼不公平
I'm just saying it's unfair to Manny.
那孩子只靠自己是没希望赢的
The kid doesn't stand a chance on his own.
我要插手了
I'm tagging in here.
杰 他不需要你插手
Jay, he doesn't need you to baby him.
我就给他一点点指导而已
I'm just gonna give him a few tips.
孩子 去吃点东西
Kid, get yourself a snack.
好吧 我给他切点葡萄
Okay, I'll cut him some grapes.
别捣乱
Damn it!
不是那种切片 杰
Not like that, Jay.
是这样 瞧着
Like this. Look.
那个能惹毛我 你懂的
It just irritates me, you know what I mean?
我们近期在见一些孕妇 以预备将来领养
We're meeting with prospective birth mothers.
我们曾有过一些类似的见面
We've had a few of these meetings,
那种事让人十分伤脑筋
and they're very nerve-racking.
你希望打扮得帅气迷人
You want to look good,
给对方留下良好的第一印象
You want to make a good first impression
有点像初次约会
kind of like a first date.
事实上 跟初次约会正好相反
Actually, it's--it's the opposite of a first date.
你不想做爱 但却希望直接要个孩子
You don't wanna have sex, but you do want a baby.
我必须承认 莉莉太可爱了
I have to say, Lily is adorable,
而且很能吃哦
and such a good eater.
并非总是如此
Oh, not all the time.
她只是喜欢我做的金枪鱼沙拉而已
She just happens to love my tuna salad.
当然 我们没吃海豚
Dolphin safe, of course.
谁在乎那个啦
Oh, who cares about that?
我觉得海豚们介意
Well, I bet the dolphins do.
你意思是说吃金枪鱼可以 吃海豚就不行
It's okay to eat tuna, but not dolphin?
我却觉得 鱼就是鱼而已
My theory is, a fish is a fish.
其实呢
Well...
海豚实际上是哺乳动物 所以说
A dolphin's actually a mammal, so...
就像番茄和西红柿 都一回事
Eh, to-may-to, to-mah-to.
那番茄和母牛还一回事呢
More like tomato, cow.
米奇 来厨房帮我弄一下司康饼
Mitchell, can you help me with the scones in the kitchen?
好的
Okay.
失陪一下
Excuse us.
好吧 我们不是来弄司康饼的
Okay, this is not really about the scones.
是吗 你一个人能拿得了六块饼吗
Oh, really? You didn't need help carrying six scones?
不 问题是你得改掉
No, this is about your need to correct
偏执地纠正别人小错误的毛病
everyone's every little mistake.
不好意思
I am sorry.
但我觉得她需要学习一些基础生物知识
I thought that she could use a basic biology lesson.
好吧 我来告诉你一点基础生物知识
Well, let me give you a basic biology lesson--
你跟我生不了孩子
you and I can't make a baby.
所以如果她指着一盏灯 说那是乔治叔叔
So if she points to a lamp and calls it "Uncle George,"
你怎么说
What are you gonna say?
"很高兴见到你 乔治叔叔"
"Pleased to meet you, Uncle George."
很好 现在我们出去
Very good. Now let's get out there,
微笑 点头 弄个孩子回来
smile, nod, and get ourselves a baby.
好吧
Okay.
眼前就是你们的五把钥匙[关键要点]
And those are your five keys.
如果没有别的问题的话
Now if there are no more questions...
哦看 这边有位可爱的买家
Ah, yes, the lovely home buyer right here
正跃跃欲试呢
On the edge of her seat.
我想问的是
I was wondering...
I was wondering,
有第六把钥匙吗
Is there a sixth key?
事实上
As a matter of fact,
的确有
There is.
待会儿得再练练
We'll work on that.
此乃你能够以低于市场价买到新居的关键
It's the key to the new home you've purchased below market.
感谢沃斯南&肯尼利&邓菲公司吧
Thanks to Woosnum, Keneally, and Dunphy.
精彩绝伦
Bravo!
放彩花 落帷幕
Fire the confetti cannon, drop the banner,
签名 签名 签名
autographs, autographs, autographs,
然后搞定
and we're done.
我们还剩一个小时呢
We still have, like, an hour left.
我能去购物吗
Can I go shopping?
不行 我得做一些发声练习
No. I-I have vocal exercises to do,
我需要你帮我检查一下嗓音
and I need you to do a sound check for me.
我打算和海莉去一趟发廊来着
I was hoping we could go to my hair salon.
就在附近 今天早上我没时间弄头发
It's nearby. I didn't have time to finish my hair this morning.
不是吧 就要弃我而去了吗
Really? That just happens?
真好 我可以去做美甲
Ooh, and I can get my nailse done.
行吗
Is it okay?
好吧 走吧
Okay. Sure.
对了
Oh, oh!
你们出去时谁能把这个钉在某一个椅子下面
Could one of you guys stick this under a chair on your way out?
某个幸运参会者可以带回家
One of the lucky attendees is going home
一个新型鼠标垫哦
with a brand-new mouse pad.
等一下 等一下
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
我不想知道是哪个椅子
I don't wanna see which chair.
我想到时候和其他人一样被震撼到
I wanna be blown away like everyone else.
没错 那就叫顺应风水
Yes. Now that is feng shui.
现在是不是感觉舒服多了
Doesn't that feel better?
还真是 现在的格局"真适合"聊天
Oh, yes. It's wonderful for conversation.
没错 感觉真好
Yes, this is nice.
让室内有一种流通感 我真的好喜欢
It gives the room a nice flow, which I'm really liking.
有时候 你的家具会告诉你 它们想被放在哪里
Sometimes, your furniture tells you where it wants to be.
对
Yeah.
我能用一下卫生间吗
Do you mind if I use your restroom?
请 大厅一直走就是
Not at all. It's-- it's just down the hall.
顺便说一下 里面有些家具
Just be warned--there's some furniture in there
貌似就喜欢现在的摆放位置哦
that kind of likes where it is!
好吧 我明白让你如此卑躬屈膝装孙子很折磨人
Okay, I know it's killing you to do this whole song and dance,
但是我觉得进行的很顺利
But I think it's going great.
小卡 得有个度才行 懂吗
Cam, there's a limit, okay?
我们已经答应会带她儿子逛遍52个州
We already promised her that we would show her son all 52 states.
哇哦 你们还有电子琴耶
Oh, wow, you have a keyboard.
是的 那是我的琴
Oh, yes. That's mine.
你是音乐家 我喜欢
You're musical. I love that.
那对我很重要
It's very important to me.
噢 还用你来向我鼓吹音乐的重要性嘛
Oh, well, you're preaching to the choir.
真的 我真在几个唱诗班唱过呢
Literally. I've sung in several.
我们经常 给莉莉唱歌
Yeah, we sing to Lily... all of the time.
我真希望能听听你们的歌声
I wish I could hear you guys.
噢哈 谢谢夸奖
Oh, well, that's very sweet.
不是 我现在想听
No, now.
宝宝的亲生父亲是个音乐家
The baby's father is a musician,
所以我真的很希望
and I would love to know
他能在一个音乐氛围浓厚的家庭成长
that he's growing up in a musical househo.
-好吧 -太好了
- Okay. - Great.
好吧 现在我们真得歌舞欢腾了
Okay. Now we are actually doing a song and dance.
好吧 你应该这么想
Okay, well, look at it this way--
我们不仅是是领养了一个宝宝
We're not only adopting a baby,
也避免了他将一生都用于寻找东达科他州
we're saving it from a life spent searching for east Dakota.
神啊
Oh, God.
这灯其实不错的
This is acally nice.
用来靠着确实挺不错的
This is actually very nice to lean on.
又摔破了
It broke again.
是啊 我看见了
Mm. Yes, I saw.
我们只需要把棉层加倍就好了
We'll just need to double up on the cotton.
瞧着 反正都是碎 不如直接摔
Here, let me save you a step.
艾丽克斯
Alex!
开门开门
Knock, knock!
爸爸 你来这干什么
Dad! Hey! What are you doing here?
曼尼需要用我借给菲尔的电烙铁
Manny needs that solder iron I lent to Phil.
他那装置上的一个螺钉总是拧不紧
One of the screws on his project keeps coming loose.
除了那个毛病 其余的就无懈可击了
Other than that, it's flawless.
最新的一次测试中 他在楼顶松手后
Huh. His latest test run, he dropped it off the roof,
走下楼梯 这时候鸡蛋还没落地呢
he walked downstairs, it hadn't landed yet.
我毫无进展 我必须扰乱克莱尔的方寸
I had nothing. I had to get in Claire's head.
有时候想要在竞争中拔得头筹
Sometimes the best thing to do in race to the top...
最好是玩点阴的
is grease the pole behind you.
这么说 曼尼还在做吗
Wow. So Manny's still working?
卢克几小时之前就完成了
Luke finished a couple hours ago.
所以地上才有这么多烂鸡蛋吗
Is that why all these eggs are on the floor?
其实是经历了多次的成功试验后
Oh, well, you know, after so many landed safely,
我们觉得应该测试一下这些鸡蛋
we thought we should test 'em,
确保这些不是超级摔不烂鸡蛋
make sure we weren't working with a super strong batch.
听起来你们相当成功嘛
Sounds like you knocked it out of the park.
那是当然
Oh yeah!We did.
那么 爸爸
Um, so dad,
如果我知道菲尔把电烙铁搁哪了
if I find out what Phil did with that soldering iron,
我就给你送去
I'll run it over.
太好了 因为
Great. . 'cause, uh,
我们今天晚些时候会在学校试验
we're gonna test it later today at the school.
有意思 说不定到时能碰见你呢
Fun. Maybe we'll meet you.
我们随时都能去 是吧
We can come anytime, right?
因为我们的弹簧什么的可没出故障
Cause we don't have a-a spring problem.
5点见
Run 5?
一言为定
Perfect.
您多担待 我们久未开过嗓了
Okay. Bear with us. We're a little rusty.
没错 请把手机调至震动状态
Yes, and please put all cell phones on vibrate.
*不要把我心伤*
*Don't go breaking my heart*
*我怎能把你心伤*
*I couldn't if I tried*
*宝贝 如果我焦躁不安*
*Honey, if I get restless*
*宝贝 你不是那种人*
*Baby, you're not that kind*
*无人知晓*
*Nobody knows it*
*Nobody knows*
*当我心潮低落*
*When I was down*
*我就是逗你笑的小丑*
*I was your clown*
我真的是个小丑
I really am a clown.
*我把心都给了你*
*I gave you my heart*
*所以不要把我心伤*
*So don't go breaking my heart*
*我不会把你心伤*
*I won't go breaking your heart*
*不要把我心伤*
*Don't go breaking my*
*不要把我心伤 耶*
*Don't go breaking my heart.Yeah*
-谢谢 -唱得太好了
- Thank you. - It was wonderful.
但是我有点疑惑
Oh. I'm confused, though.
我以为卡梅隆是歌手
I thought Cameron was the singer.
是
Yeah.
是 是 我是
Yes, yes, I am.
真的 因为米奇尔的嗓音那么甜美
Really? Because mitchell has such a lovely voice.
其实 我想是他只是跟着我的调
Well, I think he was following my lead.
一个好的领唱可以带动全场呢
You know, a good leader can make all the difference.
事实上 你的音不太准
Actually, you were a little pitchy.
但总体真的很棒 真的
But it was terrific, really.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你的点评
Yes. Thank you for your opinion.
快点 快点 你爸那边要迟到了
Faster! Faster! We're going to be late to your father.
为什么你还得给你的脚趾头做美甲
Why did you have to do your toes, too?
学校里有个超可爱的男生
Well, there's this really cute boy at school
好像有点迷上我的玉足了呢
who's kinda into my feet.
小心点 说不定那人是个变态
Be careful. That can get really creepy fast.
咦 车呢 我刚就停这了
Ay. Where is the car? I parked it here!
这是禁停区
It's a tow zone.
那牌子肯定是刚刚挂上的
Somebody just put that there,
因为我停车的时候还没有那块牌呢
because that wasn't here when I parked!
我觉得那块牌已经风吹日晒很久了啊
It looks pretty old to me.
海莉 别瞎说 刚刚真没那块牌
Haley, don't lie. That was not here!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
准备好欢迎
Get ready for one of the giants
房地产行业巨子
of residential real estate...
推销员中的推销员
A salesman's salesman...
你们在哪 我刚刚一直给你们打电话
Where are you guys? I've been calling you!
房产经纪人中的翘楚
A realtor's realtor...
本该由你来引入我的出场
You were supposed to do my intro.
现在只能我自己干了
Now I have to.
两届非连续年度房地产经纪人奖得主
2-time non-consecutive winner of the realtor of the year award...
在活动尾声时务必回来
Just get back here by the end.
未来的投资者们
Future investors,
别再找借口了
Stop making excuses!
开始 让你们的梦想成真
And start... making your dreams come true!
女士们先生们 有请菲尔·邓菲
Ladies and gentlemen, Phil Dunphy!
你们好吗
How are you?
谢谢 麦克 多谢了
Thanks, Mike. I appreciate it.
欢迎各位
Welcome.
计程车
Taxi!
看到没 见我是拉美裔就不停车
You see? They don't stop because I'm latina.
或者因为那是辆黄色私家小轿车
Or because that was just a yellow car.
我爸肯定气坏了
My dad is gonna freak out.
你得把错都揽在自己身上
You have to take the blame for this.
为什么
Why me?
因为他永远不会生你的气
Oh, because he'll never get mad at you.
他把你当女神一样膜拜
He totally puts you on a pedestal.
才不是呢
That's not true.
就是
Yeah, it is.
我打电话到计程车公司叫车吧
Let me just call the cab company.
计程车
Taxi!
有那么难找吗 各位 红色的小卡片而已
It's not rocket science, people, it's just a little red card.
好吧 看来没人需要鼠标垫
Okay. I guess nobody needs a mouse pad.
我最爱的女儿在做什么呢
How's my favorite kid doing?
最爱
Favorite?
我知道 父母不该偏爱哪个孩子
Yeah, I know, we're not supposed to have favorites.
可事实是 我们的确有偏爱
But you know what? We do.
好消息是 宝贝疙瘩就是你
And the good news is, it's you.
我不会把我的设计给你的
I'm not giving you my design.
谁说要你白给了
Who said anything about giving?
可以商量下条件嘛
We can work out an arrangement.
你这是作弊
It's cheating.
你想要什么 钱吗
What do you want? Money?
我有点私房钱
I got a little something set aside.
好吧 我根本不该给你提示的
Okay. I shouldn't even be giving you this hint,
但是 首先找面镜子
but, first get a mirror.
镜子
A mirror?
接着你看向镜子
Then you're gonna look in it,
你会看到一个疯婆子
and you're gonna see a crazy woman.
她需要你的帮助
She needs your help.
我产出的卵子[蛋]创造了你
You know, I made the egg that made you,
你又产出了那个科学设计
that made that project,
说来说去 你的设计本来就是属于我的
so in a lot of ways, that design is already mine!
你挺好的
Oh, you're fine.
大家确定没有任何问题了吗
Are you sure that there are no more questions?
没问题了吗 很好
No more questions? Yes!
请将麦克风递给那位大胡子先生
If we could just get that over to the mustachioed gentleman.
我想问
Yes, I was--
这声音大家都听烦了吧
Oh, hey, I think we're all tired of that sound.
我走过来好了
Let me just come to you.
我敢肯定我知道你想问什么
I bet I know what your question is.
你可能好奇
You're probably wondering
有第六把钥匙吗
if there's sixth key.
不 我是想问
No, I was wondering about--
我是想问关于加急契约的问题
I was wondering about accelerated escrow.
如果买卖双方都愿意
If it works for both parties,
可以加快过户速度
it's a great way to expedite the deal.
回到你第一个问题
But back to your first question
神秘的第六把钥匙
about this mysterious sixth key.
-我没说... -第六把钥匙
- I didn't say anything-- - The sixth key is the key
就是以低于市场价购入新房的关键
to the new home that you purchased below market.
利用你们今天所学到的简单原理
Using the simple principles that you learned here today...
也不是那么简单 你们依然需要
But not so simple that you don't still need
专业的房地产公司的服务
the professional services
即沃斯南&肯尼利&邓菲公司
of Woosnum, Keneally... And Dunphy!
感谢各位的光临
Thank you for coming.
你妹的...
Son of a--
关于我们 你还想了解什么
So is--is there anything that you'd like to know about us?
我看不用了
I don't think so.
事实上 我觉得不用再面试其他人了
In fact, I don't think I need to interview any more people.
你们太合适了
You guys are perfect.
你的意思是像我想的那样吗
Are--are you saying what I think you're saying?
我不应该直接对你们说什么
I'm not supposed to say anything to you directly,
但是 你们就等着好消息吧
but I think you guys should be expecting good news.
我的天啊
Aah! Oh, gosh!
了解 了解 你什么都没说
Oh, I know, I know, you're not saying anything!
但你没说出口的话 是天大的好消息
But what you're not saying is wonderful!
好了 我去拿起泡苹果酒
Um, all right. I'm gonna get some sparkling cider?
好的 好的
Yes, yes. Okay, okay.
没有苹果酒就没有庆祝氛围
It wouldn't be a celebration without cider
没有庆祝之歌也一样
or a celebratory song.
不过这次 我希望你坐在这里
But this time, I want you to sit right here.
坐下吧
So have a seat here.
把你乱掉的头发拂到肩后
Let's just get this mop out of the way there.
*如果你现在离我而去*
*If you leave me now*
*你将带走我人生的大部分意义*
*You'll take away the biggest part of me*
*不要 宝贝 求你别走*
*Ooh, ooh, ooh, no, baby, please don't go*
*不要 我只想要你留下*
*Ooh, ooh, ooh, no, I just want you to stay*
没错 她很伤心 不过往好处想
Yes, she was upset, but on a positive note,
从此事中得到的结论就是 我的歌声很能打动人
what I take from this experience is, I can sing.
从此事中我们没得到的 是孩子
Uh, what we didn't take away from the experience is a baby,
人家决定留下孩子自己养
Because she decided to keep it.
不好 我们完全错过了吗
No. Did we missed everything?
是的 来宾都迅速退场了
Yeah. They cleared out of here pretty fast.
扫兴
Bummer.
又岂止扫兴 海莉
More than a bummer, Haley.
此次推广对我来说很重要 却被你弄砸了
This was really important to me, and you blew it.
不 菲尔 全是我的错
Ay, no, Phil, it was my fault.
不关她的事
It was not her fault.
算了 木已成舟
Okay. What's done is done.
你把宣传册子拿上车吧
Can you take the brochures out to the car?
满满一盒都没动
Wow. It's still full.
是的
Yeah, it is.
推广效果不好吗
So it was not very good?
不好
Um... no.
我得打扫这里
I kind of need to sweep here.
好的 不过我真的很抱歉 菲尔
Okay. But--but I'm so sorry, Phil.
没关系
It's okay.
不 有关系
No, it's not okay.
我们迟到了 我们毁了你的解说会
We came late and we ruined your whole presentation.
人都有倒霉的时候
These things happen.
没错 可这个时候一般人都会发火
Yeah, it happens, and people get angry.
歌洛莉亚 没事的
Gloria, it's fine.
不 有事
No, it's not fine!
我努力与你沟通
I'm trying to have a real conversation,
而你却把我当女神一样膜拜
and all you do is put me on a pedestal!
等等 你在生我的气吗
Wait a minute. You'mad at me?
是的 因为家人之间
Yes, because that's not how family's
不应该是这种态度
supposed to treat each other!
你知道家人之间应该是什么态度吗
You know how family's supposed to treat each other?
家人之间应该为对方考虑
They're supposed to actually think about each other!
我求你帮一个忙
I asked you to do one thing...
但你却这么自私 这么不负责任
And you were too selfish and irresponsible
连一天都不支持我 信不信由你
to come through for me on a day that, believe it or not,
今天对我真的很重要
was really important to me!
天哪 你居然哭了 真对不起
Oh, my god. You're crying. I'm so sorry.
不 这正是我想要的
No! That's what I want!
你吼我是因为爱我
You yell at me because you love me!
你惹我生气了嘛
Well, you made me mad.
你生气也是应该的
And you should be.
好吧 我已经不气了
Well, I'm not anymore.
别把我不当家人嘛 菲尔
Don't treat me like that, Phil.
因为我现在出离愤怒了
Because now I'm furious!
噢 这才是我的亲人
Ay, mi familia! Si.
你怎么能这样呢
Oh, how do you do that?
你真是...
It makes me so...
气死我了
Mad.
对一个13岁孩子来说 手工做的相当不错啊
That's a pretty nice piece of handiwork for a 13-year-old.
是啊 卢克做的也很好啊
Yeah, Luke did pretty good, too,
毕竟平时他脱下书包都需要人帮助
for a kid who still needs help getting out of his backpack.
-他可是您外孙啊 -怒其不争啊
- Still your grandson. - Felt bad when I said it.
我们开始吧
Okay, let's do this.
孩子们看着点儿 扔下来了哦
Watch out, kids! They're coming down!
一 二 三
One, two, three.
怎么样
How'd we do?
两只蛋都完好无损
Both eggs are okay.
太好了 看来我们都是赢家
Great. So we both win.
无法接受
Unacceptable.
我们升级一层楼吧
We're going up another level.
没错 来吧 三楼了哈
Absolutely. Come on. Third floor.
艾丽克斯 上来找我们 走吧
Meet us there, Alex. Let's go.
等等
Wait.
没这必要啊
You don't have to do this.
作业是从一层楼高扔下来就行的
The assignment was for a 1-story drop.
我们都能得到A
We both get A's.
就按我们说的办
We're doing this.
真讨厌
I don't like this.
他俩在一起一合计
The two of them talking up there--
肯定会发现我们的诡计
they're gonna figure out what we did.
我们是迫不得已
We did what we had to.
我们会被抓现行的
We're gonna get caught.
看看他们
Look at them down there.
他俩压根就不关心
They're not even paying attention.
现在才是最精彩的嘛
This is the best part.
事实上 曼尼好像挺不乐意的
Actually, Manny looks kind of upset.
他不乐意啥 他马上要让卢克好看了哎
Why would he be? He's about to kick Luke's butt.
拉倒吧
Oh, knock it off.
卢克和曼尼在这个项目中根本毫无付出
Luke and Manny had as much to do with this project
就好比曼哈顿计划跟他们完全无关一样
as they did with the Manhattan Project.
你觉得是这么回事吗
You think that's what's going on?
他们烦是因为我们抢了他们的活儿
They're upset because we took over for them?
也许吧
Maybe.
他们本该从中学到东西
They were supposed to--to learn from this,
却被我们毁的干干净净
and--and we ruined it.
-我们应该去跟他俩谈谈 -没错
- We should go talk to them. - Yeah.
孩子们 我们谈谈吧
Boys, we need to talk.
天哪 天啊
Oh, god. Oh, god.
淡定点
Just stay frosty.
我们明白了一些事情
So, uh, we realized couple things up there,
我觉得该道歉了
and I think apologies are in order.
好吧 我们坦白
Ok, we admit it.
我们使计让你们替我们做这个任务来着
We tricked you into doing our projects for us.
什么
What?
我也是才知道的
This is the first I'm hearing of this.
我们知道如果要让你们把活儿全都揽下来
We knew you'd do all the work
就得让你们之间相互较劲儿
if you thought you were competing with each other.
所以我告诉你 克莱尔可能在帮卢克的忙
So I told you I thought Claire was helping Luke,
然后你就打给了克莱尔
and then you called Claire...
所以就这么把我扯进来了...
which got me involved, and...
行了 接下来这样子
All right. Here's what's gonna happen--
你给我上车 我们马上开车回家
You're gonna get in the car, we're gonna drive home,
然后你们各做各的 自己动手
and you're each gonna do your own projects.
好吧
Fine.
说到底 都是你的错
You know, this is your fault.
什么
What?
我们父女一直争来争去 太病态了
The way we compete with each other it's--is sick.
极度不正常 就连俩十三岁的孩子
It's so sick, two 13-year-olds
都知道怎么利用我们这点
Know how to take advantage of us.
而且 其实 是你把我变成这样的
And you know what? You made me this way.
你怎么能这么想
How do you figure that?
老爸 你逼着我参加体育运动
Dad! You pushed me into sports.
但却从来不让我赢 这种事情
You never let me win. You know, that stuff--
对女孩子是会有影响的
it does something to a girl.
在我看来 你天生就是这么争强好胜啊
For your information, you came out of the womb like that.
我有时都怀疑 你妈怀的是不是双胞胎
I'm not entirely sure there wasn't a twin in there
另一个被你在子宫里干掉了
you bumped off.
如果你早看出我这性格 为何不纠正我
If you saw that in me, why didn't you discourage it?
我为什么要纠正我爱的东西
Why would I discourage something that I love?
真的吗
Really?
开什么玩笑
You kidding?
你可是个斗士
You're a fighter.
我爱的就是你这种永不放弃的个性
The thing I love about you is you never give up.
老爸
Dad.
尽管我的设计明显比你的好
Even though I clearly designed a superior egg container.
又在说疯话 老头
Out of your mind, old man.
只有一种方法能证明
Only one way to find out.
放弃吧
Give up.
你俩再怎么争都只能得第二
You're all just playing for second.
那妞也遗传了点不正常基因
There's something wrong with that one.
我才没有不正常
I'm not wrong.
老妈有时候很疯狂 对吧
Mom can be crazy, right?
喂
Hello!
谢谢你
Thank you.
但是生她气的同时 我也挺内疚的
At the same time, I feel guilty when I get mad at her.
我不觉得那算古怪啊
I don't think that's weird.
我真为我的手工骄傲
Just really proud of my project.
我可不想与人分享
I don't wanna share it.
每个人都有自己的癖好嘛
Everybody has his own thing.
谢谢你 海莉
Thanks, Haley.
我知道这么说挺傻的
I know it might sound dorky,
但与你的深夜长谈对我来说很有意义
but this late-night conversations really mean a lot to me.
只有在此时我才觉得...
They're the only time that I feel like I...
好吧 科瑞 就一张照片哦
Ok, Corey, just one picture.
稍等
Hold on.
从这个角度看我的脚好胖啊
My feet look fat from this angle.
艾丽克斯 醒醒
Hey, Alex, wake up.
帮忙给我的脚拍张照片吧
I need you to take a picture for my feet.